I will create the stock simulation extension, so I will use like a deep research.
We can make a deep research, maybe thinking mode.
I think I think it mode is enough and we can also add like a web research.
And I will use the thinking so first, I want to create a Chrome extension that will
simulate stock mechanism if artificial money, and let us quickly check simulation based
on simple request to open source APIs, provide me and tell to do list and potential possibilities.
So let's ask about it and we see if it can do, what level are in the trading, long term.
I would say a long term portfolio tracking, although we can do in the trading, and then
introduce this coming to web profiles or share simulation space, individual profiles.
I want stock price, volumes and brief companion info, historical data, like one week, one month,
six months year, five year, and to revisit the stock Chrome on my ball show, I want to keep
it only as an extension, I don't need communication aspects, I want some achievements
take first 1000 and some later plans for investing 1000 and some related ones.
So I will just make it maybe by number, so it will be easier to understand, always in bullet
points, it is not clear, but it will just understand, and I will keep it as there is, and
then we will try it.
It is starting research, and then I will use the research to create an app, the instructions
have been provided, we have a Chrome extension stack simulator, first we need to project
setup, create a new Chrome extension, include manifest JSON, and then some permission for
APIs.
So it is that instruction and creating new folder open the cursor and now creating new
folder, so let me open it up, it is here, I will open the project, I will go to Chrome
cars, I will open a new extension and we can name it as it was, so we can name it Chrome
extension stack simulator, so go here again and I will name it Chrome extension stack
simulator, so I will use the folder, I will open it up, and now when it is ready, now
we can use maybe agent, and I will open maybe two tab, static ring, so as you can see
I can even make it, so the first agent will just create project setup, I will create
a Chrome extension stack simulator, let's start with this, and I can set here, let's
place all those, so this is the first agent, he work on it, it is creating the first
stop up, we need to already creating, so, okay, I will always stand here, so it will create
like a folder for icons that will be here, not sure if you can, it doesn't can generate
icons, but it can just try to connect it directly from there, okay, and we can keep it
as it is for now, I will just focus on it, so this is the terminal, this is the file,
and I will keep the main one, extension is ready to use, the next thing I will use interface,
and I will see we can return to each one to return the sender suppress this one, so
I should review it, update the JavaScript to handle the new UI features, it has been finished
here, it is great, we can keep it for now, so here we have an API key, and then we can implement
that effect, you log to the logic client, so we will just get some request, and our manifest
file, which is the main one, and we can find it, and here just so it has to have permission,
so you edit, I mean you ask to edit, I will just wait until it is done, and then we will
just try to make it, as you can see it is updating, okay, we see some features, and now
I will just ask about data fetching, so I will just enter this, and we can run a new agent
about displaying a price chart, so for it we can use a charge of a script for now, a chart,
so as a new one, and I can use it, so we can use like the agents and rename it, so this
is like a rename, and we can set create an empty extension, so to do a walk like this,
this is we can name it like API, and then this we can create charts, so we didn't able
to know, and then obviously we can just go to each agent, then go to the direct place,
and press continue, I can just focus on now, this is on top of your panel, but we can still
use it, you know, so if I open it here, I'll toggle, I can have a server, or open it in
different direction, so it's here, we can only see pin it up, or I'll just minimize and
the chat, so it's up to us, okay, I'll just run it to have it, and I will return it to
main one, so do create a chart, do visualize it, okay, it's done, actually it's very quick,
now I'll just implement, implement analytics, so it will use like Chrome alarms, it's great
because we know the work was even if you don't know anything about the Chrome extension,
it still shows what it can use, and this way, obviously we have a here reference to the
main website, but when you copy it over, it's just like a plain instruction, so I'll model,
it's not getting lost in the meantime, all right, you have a summary, that's great,
so go down, it's still creating a pop-up, but then after that, we see some of it, and
the last query will be user portfolio, it's multiple portfolios,
and then I will copy the last entry, and go here, and now I'm in the new agent in the
meantime, because I would like to add some achievements and gamification, so there will
be a query word system to motivate somehow an engagement people will be able to get some
of it, and I will just pass it, and after the new chat, it will create a new agent, and
now we'll rename it to gamification, and as well, gamify learning features like enhancement,
menu challenges, and learning tools, it will be the same one, and last but not least,
we will try to stream my adding stocks, so it will be like persisting data here, and then
the testing and iteration will be like the last agent that I would like to run, so you
can even open a new agent, and I'd like a streamline, so it will be like a lookup in
datum, I'll enter it, and rename it, as you can see, it's working really fast, and I'm
switching between number there, and stuff, I think it's still adding, adding a pop-up
sounds, down, chart is done, gamification is being added, this is lookup data, so for this
one, we see the new stuff, API has been finished, so we see the call structure, this is
the gamification that we are adding, and gamify learning files, you can see, okay, build
your word system, and this is the charts, it's still loading sometimes, it can take some
time, but by default it uses composer, here I'm using like a composer, so it makes it fast,
it's a terminal, I'm sure why it's running, but I can't walk as it is, and then we can
open a new agent, so this is gamification that was finished, so this is the jimbit reward system,
and you can add like a this thing to it, and for API I think it's enough, this is not
useful for on us, we still see like it works in on chart, and lookup data, stock lookup,
we have it here, it's still adding, but then I'll add, persisting data from usage, and after
the tag agent for attesting mode, okay, we see the summary, so now I'm going to, I think
it's better to check, but I would now showing how we can combine to DPT, and then obviously
we can try to search and look for each agent, especially if we don't define what is the error,
so we can use and this, and we can run a new agent, because as you can see chart was
a bit finished, so the last agent will be about testing, test if Chrome extension is working
by the end, but first we have to look if it's added because it's still working on a new one,
and after it's finished, we'll be able to go back and just try to use it.
It's down with gamification, it's down with lookup data, and I can just run a new agent,
and I would just test it, I think it disappeared, so I'll just go back, test the whole extension
by the end, because whole habit to Chrome after to test it myself, and I'll use it again,
obviously we can use the list inside of it, but this is the another approach when we can ask
like chart GPT to specify the list of the task to do it, we can try to do it in one run,
and I will show in one of the extension how it will look different, because now we just
make each agent for each functionality, how continue, you create placeholder icons,
and syntax, and after we'll be able to see if the extension is working for our case.
Trying period, so we'll just load and back extension,
stuck simulator, and obviously we don't have an icons, so I will just copy from other ones,
because I don't want to create a receiver, you can use the AI to create it, but now we'll just use
something else, so we'll just go to extension simulator, just copy it over, and now when you upload
and this stock simulator, I'll just use it, as you can see, it has been added, so now I'll just
open it up, this our stock simulator, and we see our portfolio, wow that's great, so we see return,
we see how it's starting money, in the options we can use default, we can create a profile like risk,
and if I create a profile, I think it's already done, so if it's a risk, I can switch the risk,
and then I can look for some stock, so I'll just use the APL, I think it's the API,
and you can go here, so we can please set your API key in settings, so first we need to
ahead our API key, a fan of BI key, so we have to go to this financial mode,
and here how we can get it, we just get some API, so I use alpha vintage, and now we go to extension,
I'll go here refresh, stock simulator as well, and I'll open it up now, I have a risk,
so I have train analysis, analytics, portfolio, there is no stocks in portfolio,
and now I see it provides it, so I can use Apple, and then here I have a chart, I have everything,
and we can buy some shorts, for example like five shirts, and then when you apply, it's
same forecast, and then when you go to portfolio, I see my cash balance, and then I can see
the progress, it's a very nice extension, I think it's pretty much good, especially if you want to
see how our alternative portfolios perform without losing any real money.